lucio chen

UX/UI designer & web developer

profile

I value the usability and simplicity of the design. My mission is to create elegant designs for apps and websites that give users an enjoyable experience in the interaction.

skills

Design skills

UI/UX design Graphic design

User research

Tools

Illustrator Photoshop Figma Adobe XD

After Effect Maya

Premier

Development

HTML/CSS

Javascript

Java

Other skills

Video Editina

3D modelling

interactive design experiences

UI/UX design: Tool library showcase UX/UI design, Graphic design, User research

(Course: Interactive Design Methods)

 Applied many research tools in the client touch base and user research to have an accurate understanding of our client and their problem.

- Explored different design solutions that are grounded in our user data. Finally, chose the most feasible solution to make the organization more engaging for its members.
- Communicated regularly with the client to understand client's constraint and refined our project based on their feedback.

Interface redesign: Peeknest

2019 Fall

Spring 2020

UI/UX design, User Research

(Course: User Interface Design)

- Conducted multiple user testings on this existing app in the research term. Found out the flaws in usability and knew how its functionality mismatch users' needs.
- Prototyped the refined user interface, tried out a different solution of feature integration to reach the best result that presents the function of this app correctly.



luciochen.github.io



(a) luciochen79@gmail.com



778-772-3973

education

Simon Fraser University

BA of Interactive Arts and Technology

Fall 2017 - Summer 2021

SIAT teaches design theories and skills that can be applied in multiple fields. It provides practices of design skills, communication, and collaboration skills in team projects.

award

Dean's honor roll

Fall 2018

in Simon Fraser University

(Term GPA 3.5 or higher with at least 12 term credits)

employment

Coco Fresh Tea & Juice

Role: Barista

June 2019 - Dec 2020

- Communicated with customers about their in-store experience. The feedback was then implemented to improve our customer service.
- Observed the team's working process and assisted other team members when problems came up, which successfully reduced errors in busy hours.

Jinya Ramen Bar

Role: Food Prep

Oct 2017 - Jan 2018

• Co-operated with the team members sufficiently, made adjustment on the workflow based on the team's goal and current situation.